<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Home on ThirdAI</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on ThirdAI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//thirdailabs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Test</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/test/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 11:27:24 -0600</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/test/</guid><description>This is a page for testing new features, content, and animations. It is a draft page and as such, it will never be rendered on the production website. You can find the corresponding layout file in /layouts/test/single.html and the corresponding stylesheet in /assets/css/common/test.css.</description></item><item><title>Training Bottlenecks: A Harsh Reality of AI Models</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/blog/training-bottlenecks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/blog/training-bottlenecks/</guid><description>There is no silver bullet AI modality. Better predictions require a constant cycle of feature engineering, hyper-parameter tuning, training, and testing the resultant models. The most time-consuming stage of any AI-powered application pipeline is fine tuning, which often requires repeated iterations of network training to expose performance gains. Even with AutoML and Neural Architecture Search (NAS), engineering features and hammering out other task-specific pipelines in an AI system is unavoidable.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/about/</guid><description>Squeezing more out of chips with algorithm and software innovations.</description></item><item><title>AI Engineer</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/engineer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/engineer/</guid><description>Location: Houston, TX
We are hiring AI Engineers (at all levels) who are strong in C++, Python, and parallel programming. If you want to build the next generation of artificial intelligence tools from scratch, get in touch!
Successful recruits will be compensated with a competitive salary, employee stock options, 401K matching, and benefits. We look forward to receiving your application!
Minimum Qualifications: Bachelors/Masters/PhD in computer science or closely related field Expertise in parallel programming, high performance computing, and machine learning system design Proficiency in C++ Broad understanding of neural networks and machine learning Preferred Qualifications: Track record of publications in leading AI venues (NeurIPS, ICML, ICLR, AAAI), leading systems venues (SIGMOD, VLDB), or their juncture (MLSys) Proficiency in Python Experience with cloud AI services (on AWS/Azure) and open-source AI/ML libraries (e.</description></item><item><title>BOLT</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/engine/bolt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/engine/bolt/</guid><description>BOLT engine provides an easy-to-use and efficient deep learning library powered by sparse coding.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/contact/</guid><description>We&amp;#39;d love to hear from you.</description></item><item><title>Contact Confirmation</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/contact-confirmation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/contact-confirmation/</guid><description>Thank you for reaching out. Our team will get in touch with you within a couple days.</description></item><item><title>Demo Confirmation</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/demo-confirmation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/demo-confirmation/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;ve received your request. You should receive an email shortly with a link to download your unique license file.</description></item><item><title>Product Recommendation</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/product-recommendation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/product-recommendation/</guid><description>The BOLT engine can train a 1.6-billion parameter model on a &amp;lt;$1,200 refurbished V3 Intel machine faster than four top-of-the-line Nvidia A100 GPUs.</description></item><item><title>Question Answering and Information Retrieval</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/question-answering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/question-answering/</guid><description>Our BOLT engine obtains the speed and scalability of lexical search with the accuracy of the best deep learning approaches for question answering.</description></item><item><title>Register for a License</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/demo/</guid><description>We&amp;#39;re glad you&amp;#39;re excited.</description></item><item><title>Sentiment Classification</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/text-classification/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/solutions/text-classification/</guid><description>Using BOLT to train sentiment classication models we see large gains in accuracy as well as reduction in training and inference times, drastically reducing end-to-end deployment costs.</description></item><item><title>Using the ThirdAI Library (Python)</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/documentation/installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/documentation/installation/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to try out the BOLT engine yourself, follow this guide.</description></item><item><title>VP of Engineering</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpengineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpengineering/</guid><description>Location: Houston, TX
Responsibilities: Lead and manage a team of AI engineers during the complete lifecycle of development Design and implement software from an end-user perspective Lead development of performance-critical algorithms Minimum Qualifications: Bachelors/Masters/PhD in computer science or closely related field Experience with building enterprise machine learning software applications 7+ years of experience as a Senior/Principal Engineering Manager with a direct impact on your company’s core business 7+ years of experience in leading teams of 10 or more Experience overseeing roadmap creation and strategy Expertise in high performance computing, systems, and machine learning Preferred Qualifications: Experience in scaling new businesses Strong executive presence and ability to interface with senior leaders internally and externally Ability to communicate effectively with both technical and non-technical individuals Clear written and verbal communications on highly complex topics Apply now</description></item><item><title>VP of Product</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpproduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpproduct/</guid><description>Location: Houston, TX
Responsibilities: Play a leading role in the complete lifecycle of product from definition to shipping Lead the design and implementation of products from an end-user perspective Initiate and lead the design and development of new products or verticals while prioritizing industry use cases Build product roadmaps in close coordination with internal engineering teams, prioritizing the most important features to customers while ensuring engineering feasibility Minimum Qualifications: Bachelors/Masters/PhD in computer science or closely related field Experience with building enterprise machine learning software applications 7+ years of experience as a Senior/Principal Product Manager with a direct impact on your company’s core business Experience overseeing roadmap creation and strategy Expertise in high performance computing, systems, and machine learning A keen customer focus Preferred Qualifications: Strong executive presence and ability to interface with senior leaders internally and externally Ability to communicate effectively with both technical and non-technical individuals Clear written and verbal communications on highly complex topics Ability to translate partner insights into product and operational requirements Apply now</description></item><item><title>Webinars</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/webinars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/resources/webinars/</guid><description>An archive of our live presentations.</description></item></channel></rss>