<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Engineer on Third AI</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/tags/engineer/</link><description>Recent content in Engineer on Third AI</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="//thirdailabs.github.io/tags/engineer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Engineer</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/engineer/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/engineer/</guid><description>Location: Houston, TX
We are hiring AI Engineers (at all levels) who are strong in C++, Python, and parallel programming. If you want to build the next generation of artificial intelligence tools from scratch, get in touch!
Successful recruits will be compensated with a competitive salary, employee stock options, 401K matching, and benefits. We look forward to receiving your application!
Minimum Qualifications: Bachelors/Masters/PhD in computer science or closely related field Expertise in parallel programming, high performance computing, and machine learning system design Proficiency in C++ Broad understanding of neural networks and machine learning Preferred Qualifications: Track record of publications in leading AI venues (NeurIPS, ICML, ICLR, AAAI), leading systems venues (SIGMOD, VLDB), or their juncture (MLSys) Proficiency in Python Experience with cloud AI services (on AWS/Azure) and open-source AI/ML libraries (e.</description></item><item><title>VP of Engineering</title><link>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpengineering/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>//thirdailabs.github.io/company/careers/vpengineering/</guid><description>Location: Houston, TX
Responsibilities: Lead and manage a team of AI engineers during the complete lifecycle of development Design and implement software from an end-user perspective Lead development of performance-critical algorithms Minimum Qualifications: Bachelors/Masters/PhD in computer science or closely related field Experience with building enterprise machine learning software applications 7+ years of experience as a Senior/Principal Engineering Manager with a direct impact on your company’s core business 7+ years of experience in leading teams of 10 or more Experience overseeing roadmap creation and strategy Expertise in high performance computing, systems, and machine learning Preferred Qualifications: Experience in scaling new businesses Strong executive presence and ability to interface with senior leaders internally and externally Ability to communicate effectively with both technical and non-technical individuals Clear written and verbal communications on highly complex topics Apply now</description></item></channel></rss>